// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which of these best describes an array?",
    answer: "Container of objects of similar types",
    options: [
      "A data structure that shows a hierarchical behavior",
      "Container of objects of similar types",
      "Container of objects of mixed types",
      "All of the mentioned"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "The largest element of an array index is called its",
    answer: "upper bound.",
    options: [
      "lower bound.",
      "range.",
      "upper bound.",
      "All of these."
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following concepts make extensive use of arrays?",
    answer: "Spatial locality",
    options: [
      "Binary trees",
      "Scheduling of processes",
      "Caching",
      "Spatial locality"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Let A[1...n] be an array of n distinct numbers. If i < j and A[i] > A[j], then the pair (i, j) is called an inversion of A. What is the expected number of inversions in any permutation on n elements ?",
    answer: "θ(n^2)",
    options: [
      "θ(n)",
      "θ(log(n))",
      "θ(nlog(n))",
      "θ(n^2)"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "The elements of an array are stored successively in memory cells because",
    answer: "by this way computer can keep track only the address of the first element and the addresses of other elements can be calculated",
    options: [
      "by this way computer can keep track only the address of the first element and the addresses of other elements can be calculated",
      "the architecture of computer memory does not allow arrays to store other than serially",
      "both of above",
      "none of above"
    ]
  },
  
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "The smallest element of an array's index is called its",
    answer: "lower bound.",
    options: [
      "lower bound.",
      "upper bound.",
      "range.",
      "extraction."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "How do you initialize an array in C?",
    answer: "int arr[3] = {1,2,3};",
    options: [
      "int arr[3] = (1,2,3);",
      "int arr(3) = {1,2,3};",
      "int arr[3] = {1,2,3};",
      "int arr(3) = (1,2,3);"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which of the following is the correct way to declare a multidimensional array in Java?",
    answer: "int[][]arr;",
    options: [
      "int[] arr;",
      "int arr[[]];",
      "int[][]arr;",
      "int[[]] arr;"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What are the advantages of arrays?",
    answer: "Easier to store elements of same data type",
    options: [
      "Objects of mixed data types can be stored",
      "Elements in an array cannot be sorted",
      "Index of first element of an array is 1",
      "Easier to store elements of same data type"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "In general, the index of the first element in an array is __________",
    answer: "0",
    options: [
      "0",
      "-1",
      "2",
      "1"
    ]
  },
];